<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Q1 2018 letter</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>First Quarter Update 2018</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Brookfield First Quarter 2018 Update</subject>
    <textOnly>First Quarter 2018 Update
 
Each quarter we provide an update to our investors on our investing activities and share our perspectives on our approach to investing. This quarter, we focus on our approach to global investing, which has played a significant role in enabling us to continue finding compelling investment opportunities despite a competitive environment.
 
Global Investing
 
The impact of politics on business seems to be on every investor&#39;s mind today. This is always the case to a certain extent, but Brexit, U.S. trade tariffs, NAFTA, China, Syria and others that are in daily social media and news headlines seem to be making investors even more preoccupied.

With respect to our operations, we are micro, rather than macro, investors. Of course, broad economic trends affect all of our businesses, but what is more important to our long-term success is our ability to find great businesses in good countries that will stand the test of time, irrespective of short-term politics. While in the long term, negative political situations could impact our businesses, in the short to medium term, politics are, for the most part, irrelevant to us and our business plans. In fact, the short-term noise frequently provides opportunities to acquire assets at reduced valuations (or to sell them for premium returns).

With respect to entering new countries, it takes a great deal of effort to establish our operations. We therefore try to choose countries wisely, stay forever, and grow incrementally in order to prevent mistakes early on. 

There are three important factors we always consider when entering a country. These include its size, a culture of respect for capital (also sometimes referred to as a rule of law, but it&#39;s more than that), and the ability to operate with the high global ethical standards we adhere to everywhere we do business. 

Having a global franchise provides us with an enormous competitive advantage. It offers us both diversification and the ability to find value in markets that few others operate in. This is important, as different regions go through different economic cycles at different times. Our global franchise allows us to scale up our investing activities in markets when things are tougher and returns therefore should be better. Conversely, it allows us to harvest capital in markets that are more fully priced. In all of this, the critical point is that we are able to turn ideas into actionable opportunities. 

Ensuring that we adhere to the above principles gives us a common basis to measure our successes and our mistakes. Over time, this continuously makes us better and gives us a definable competitive advantage.

GGP
 
In 2009, we acquired a 34% stake in GGP, one of the largest Class A mall operators in the U.S. Coming out of the recession, this has turned out to be a great investment and a business that is complementary to our other real estate businesses. Late last year, we made a bid to acquire the remaining 66% of GGP that we do not already own from the other shareholders. In March, after negotiations with the independent directors of GGP and their advisors, we agreed to a revised transaction and the independent directors of GGP have recommended to shareholders that they approve it. 

Our offer is approximately 61% in cash and 39% in units of Brookfield Property Partners (BPY) or shares of a newly created Brookfield Property REIT. This REIT will be economically equivalent to an investment in BPY but qualify as a U.S. REIT security. Total consideration for the equity of the non-Brookfield owned shares is $15 billion. 

To complete this transaction we partnered with a number of our investors and sold them interests in $4 billion of retail centers. We borrowed on a term basis another $5 billion and will, post-closing, sell interests in other assets to investors. This is a large transaction that has garnered a lot of media attention, given all the discussion around the future of retail. This is a good example of the type of contrarian investments we make during periods of market dislocation and when certain sectors are out of favor.

This acquisition will be transformative for BPY, creating one of the world&#39;s largest commercial real estate companies. Combining our deep operating expertise across multiple real estate sectors with GGP&#39;s portfolio of irreplaceable retail assets will enable us to unlock the value of these assets in a rapidly changing retail environment.

Notable Private Fund Transactions 
 
In the private funds world, last quarter we announced some notable investments across a number of markets. We are currently looking to close four transactions in the coming quarters, including two new private equity investments in Brookfield Capital Partners IV (&quot;BCP IV&quot;), and two initial investments in Brookfield Strategic Real Estate Partners III (&quot;BSREP III&quot;). Specifically:

In BCP IV, we agreed to acquire Westinghouse Electric Company, one of the world&#39;s leading suppliers of infrastructure services to nuclear power generating facilities for $4.6 billion, funded by BCP IV and Brookfield Business Partners. As a long-term business owner and operator of critical global infrastructure with deep facilities management capabilities, we will use our expertise to enhance Westinghouse&#39;s position as a leading global infrastructure services provider to the power generation business. 
 
Also in BCP IV, we agreed to acquire Schoeller Allibert Group B.V., one of Europe&#39;s largest manufacturers of returnable plastic packaging systems, for EUR 205 million. With an increased global focus on sustainability, waste reduction, e-commerce and logistics automation, the returnable packaging sector is positioned for meaningful growth. Our goal is to help this business expand internationally in a fast-growing market.
 
In BSREP III, we announced our intention to make our first investment for the fund in SACO, a European serviced apartment owner/operator with a 2,200 unit serviced apartment portfolio in major markets such as London, Edinburg and Amsterdam, for approximately £500 million. SACO represents our first foray into the serviced apartment sector, one we believe to be highly fragmented and undersupplied as consumers increasingly seek alternatives to traditional hotel accommodations. We plan to implement operational enhancements at the properties and expand into other markets in European gateway cities. 
 
Also in BSREP III, we announced our intention to acquire IC Campus, one of the largest developers and operators of student and young professional apartments in Europe, a market with unmet demand for this type of accommodation. Our goal is to use our operating expertise to build out the properties and scale the business in Europe.
 
And finally, late last year we sold Gazeley, a European industrial business acquired by BSREP I in 2013, to GLP, for $2.8 billion. This represented a 47% return on our investment of $508 million and was a great investment in the fast-growing logistics sector.
 

Closing
 
We remain committed to being a leading, world-class alternative asset manager. As stewards of your capital, our objective continues to be investing in high-quality assets that earn solid cash returns on equity, while emphasizing downside protection. 
As always, please do not hesitate to contact any of us should you have suggestions, questions, comments, or ideas you wish to share with us.
 


Sincerely,

 

bruce signature


J. Bruce Flatt

Chief Executive Officer

 
 

 









CAUTIONARY STATEMENT REGARDING FORWARD-LOOKING STATEMENTS AND INFORMATION

This letter to shareholders contains &quot;forward-looking information&quot; within the meaning of Canadian provincial securities laws and &quot;forward-looking statements&quot; within the meaning of Section 27A of the U.S. Securities Act of 1933, as amended, Section 21E of the U.S. Securities Exchange Act of 1934, as amended, &quot;safe harbor&quot; provisions of the United States Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995 and in any applicable Canadian securities regulations. Forward-looking statements include statements that are predictive in nature, depend upon or refer to future events or conditions, include statements regarding the operations, business, financial condition, expected financial results, performance, prospects, opportunities, priorities, targets, goals, ongoing objectives, strategies and outlook of Brookfield Asset Management Inc. and its subsidiaries, as well as the outlook for North American and international economies for the current fiscal year and subsequent periods, and include words such as &quot;expects,&quot; &quot;anticipates,&quot; &quot;plans,&quot; &quot;believes,&quot; &quot;estimates,&quot; &quot;seeks,&quot; &quot;intends,&quot; &quot;targets,&quot; &quot;projects,&quot; &quot;forecasts&quot; or negative versions thereof and other similar expressions, or future or conditional verbs such as &quot;may,&quot; &quot;will,&quot; &quot;should,&quot; &quot;would&quot; and &quot;could.&quot;

Although we believe that our anticipated future results, performance or achievements expressed or implied by the forward-looking statements and information are based upon reasonable assumptions and expectations, the reader should not place undue reliance on forward-looking statements and information because they involve known and unknown risks, uncertainties and other factors, many of which are beyond our control, which may cause the actual results, performance or achievements of Brookfield Asset Management to differ materially from anticipated future results, performance or achievement expressed or implied by such forward-looking statements and information.
 
Factors that could cause actual results to differ materially from those contemplated or implied by forward-looking statements include, but are not limited to: the impact or unanticipated impact of general economic, political and market factors in the countries in which we do business; the behavior of financial markets, including fluctuations in interest and foreign exchange rates; global equity and capital markets and the availability of equity and debt financing and refinancing within these markets; strategic actions including dispositions; the ability to complete and effectively integrate acquisitions into existing operations and the ability to attain expected benefits; changes in accounting policies and methods used to report financial condition (including uncertainties associated with critical accounting assumptions and estimates); the ability to appropriately manage human capital; the effect of applying future accounting changes; business competition; operational and reputational risks; technological change; changes in government regulation and legislation within the countries in which we operate; governmental investigations; litigation; changes in tax laws; ability to collect amounts owed; catastrophic events, such as earthquakes and hurricanes; the possible impact of international conflicts and other developments including terrorist acts and cyber terrorism; and other risks and factors detailed from time to time in our documents filed with the securities regulators in Canada and the United States.

We caution that the foregoing list of important factors that may affect future results is not exhaustive. When relying on our forward-looking statements, investors and others should carefully consider the foregoing factors and other uncertainties and potential events. Except as required by law, Brookfield Asset Management undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements or information, whether written or oral, that may be as a result of new information, future events or otherwise.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
